Privacy policy
==============

Defined terms in this Privacy Policy has the same meaning as in the Terms of Service.

It is of utmost importance for Degoo to protect its Users’ integrity. Degoo does not share the User’s personal data, except as necessary to provide the Services. In all other aspects, the User decides whether to share its personal data with others.

Degoo will process the User’s personal data in compliance with the Swedish Personal Data Act (SFS 1998:204) or the General Data Protection Regulation (EU 2016/679) (“GDPR”), whichever is applicable at the time, and this Privacy Policy. Degoo is the personal data controller regarding personal data that the User provides for the User Account or which is collected in connection with the User’s use of the Services. Notwithstanding the foregoing, the User owns and is responsible for personal data contained in the User’s Content.

Degoo encourages the User to regularly visit this Privacy Policy, as it may be updated from time to time.

###### 1 Collection of Personal Data

1.1 Degoo may ask the User to provide the following categories of personal data through the Platform: e-mail address, mobile phone number, and password.

1.2 Degoo may also ask the User to provide payment details, based on the User’s choice of payment, if the User utilizes parts of the Services associated with fees.

###### 2 Use of Personal Data

2.1 Degoo will process the User’s personal data for the purpose of providing the User with the Services, to receive payment for the User’s use of the Services and to communicate with the User within the scope of the Services. Degoo may also use automated systems to analyze the User’s personal data and the User’s Content, using techniques such as machine learning, to improve the Services and to develop new functionalities. Degoo may also send the User information regarding the Services and offers. If the User does not wish to receive such information, the User may opt-out by sending an e-mail to the address specified below.

2.2 The legal ground for processing the User’s personal data is to perform the Services and to fulfill the agreement between Degoo and the User, specifically article 6.1 b GDPR. For development purposes, to improve the Services and to provide the User with information about the Services, the legal ground is article 6.1 f GDPR.

2.3 Degoo may be required by law to disclose personal data to a third party or a regulatory authority.

2.4 Personal data that the User provides to Degoo will be securely stored for the User’s convenience, for as long as the User has a valid and active User Account. If the User wants Degoo to delete the User’s personal data or User Account, please contact Degoo using the information below.

2.5 User can also give third parties access to its information and account, such as Facebook or Instagram. Just remember that their use of such data will be governed by their privacy policies and terms.

###### 3 User’s Content

3.1 The User is considered the personal data controller for personal data contained in Content which has been uploaded or transmitted by the User or through the User’s User Account.

###### 4 Subcontractors

4.1 Degoo uses third party providers to host and provide the Services. Any subcontractor will be a data processor for the processing of personal data within the Services.

4.2 Personal data may be processed outside the EU/EEA, in accordance with applicable law.

4.3 Degoo is currently using Google Cloud Storage, Amazon Web Services and Wasabi Hot Cloud Storage to host the Services and to store personal data.

4.4 We work with trusted partners to enhance the quality and efficiency of our services, and we may provide certain non-personally-identifiable information to them from time to time.

###### 5 Cookies

5.1 Degoo uses cookie technology to make the Services easier to use. A cookie is a small data file which is transferred to the User’s computer’s hard drive when the User accesses the Services. The cookie is used to determine if the User is a first-time user or a returning user in order to provide the User with the best experience when accessing the Services. Degoo also caches data for the session, which is deleted when the User logs out from the Services. The User can deny a website the possibility to store cookies or cache data. In order to deny cookies or the caching of data, the User needs to edit the User’s browser settings. Please note that the User may experience less functionality when using the Services if the User chooses to turn off cookies or data cache.

###### 6 Security

6.1 Degoo uses adequate technical and organizational security measures to ensure that the User’s personal data is not misused, lost or unlawfully accessed. The User’s personal data will at all times be handled in accordance with the requirements of the applicable data protection law.

###### 7 User rights

7.1 Degoo takes all reasonable steps to ensure that the User’s personal data is correct and up-to-date. If the User believes that the User’s personal data stored by Degoo is incorrect, please notify and provide us with the correct data so that it can be rectified and updated. The User may also correct and update the personal data provided by the User directly by accessing the User Account. Degoo kindly asks the User to update its personal data if needed.

7.2 The User is entitled to, once a year, obtain information about the User’s personal data stored and handled by Degoo at no cost. The request must be made in writing and sent to the address below.

7.3 The User always has the right to object to Degoo’s processing of the User’s personal data. The effect may be that the User is no longer able to use the Services. Degoo will in such case stop the processing of the User’s personal data and delete the User Account.

7.4 Under GDPR, the User will have the right to data portability. In case the User wants to utilize such right, please contact Degoo by using the information below.

7.5 If the User has any inquiries regarding Degoo’s processing of the User’s personal data or use of cookies, please contact Degoo. If the User is displeased with our processing of personal data, the User may file a complaint to the Swedish Data Protection Authority.

Contact details  
Degoo Backup AB  
[\[email protected\]](https://degoo.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)  
Link to delete all data: [http://degoo.com/me/deleteaccount](https://degoo.com/me/deleteaccount)  
Östermalmsgatan 93 114 59 Stockholm  
Sweden
